Rohith K. Palakirti

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

rohithkp99@gmail.com +91 - 810 600 1785 linkedin.com/in/rohith-kp github.com/kprohith Hyderabad

Profile

Currently a sophomore at Manipal Academy of Higher Education pursuing a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science. Skilled in Python, C++, Java, HTML, CSS, Linux and ML/DL. Interested in deep learning and neural networks.

Projects

NSE-Stock Analysis using Machine Learning Jun 2019

Python for Finance

May 2019

Text Classification using TensorFlow and keras

May 2019

TicTacToe - commandline

May 2019

Clothing Classifier using TensorFlow and keras

Feb 2019

Automated Street Lighting using IoT

Dec 2018

Cloud-based Water Meter

Dec 2018

Smart Presence Sensing System using IoT

Dec 2018

Smart Irrigation System using IoT

Nov 2018

Smart Weather Monitor Using nodemcu

Nov 2018

Smart Weather Monitoring System

Nov 2018

Courses

Tensorflow Specialization deeplearning.ai

Jun 2019

Deep Learning Specialization

deeplearning.ai

Mar 2019

Self Driving Specialization

University of Toronto

May 2019

CS50 Harvard University

Sep 2018

Responsive Web Design freecodecamp

Jun 2019

Machine Learning Stanford University

Jan 2019

Learning How to Learn University of California, San Diego

Jun 2019

Education

BS Computer Science Engineering

Manipal Academy of Higher Education Aug 2018 - May 2020

Experience

Committee Member IECSE

Aug 2018 - Present Manipal

Research and Dev Intern Athena IOT Labs

Nov 2018 - July 2019 Hyderabad

Volunteering

Organizer Smart India Hackathon 2019

Feb 2019

Volunteer Revels 2019, MIT

Mar 2019

Volunteer TechTatva 2018, MIT

Sep 2018

Languages

English Native or bilingual proficiency

Hindi Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Telugu Native or Bilingual Proficiency